[Music]
excuse me yes are you studying English
no I prefer Arabic I asked you because
English is so popular thank you that's
the light of utilize some people would
just pick it up yes I know some people
are rude I always try to be polite so
July the world needs more polite people
like us I agree 100%
have you ever lost a tenner in the mail
no I haven't neither have I so they do a
good job for the money yes dude maybe we
shouldn't complain did you do the
laundry yes I did what did you wash I
washed clothes and towels what about the
pocket
no I didn't did you dry everything in
the dryer yes I dried everything in the
dryer then what did you do I folded all
the clothes
mum I'm hungry look in the fridge I'm
looking there's nothing to eat are you
sure it's almost empty I went to the
market last week I don't see anything I
bought lots of apples and grapes
I don't want fruit I want something
tasty eat the fruits it's good for you
next time you go to the market I eating
me going with you no thank you all you
want to eat a candy bars and hotdogs I
think I'll make a pizza what kind a
seafood pizza bread flour is in the
cabinet where's the shrimp it's in the
fridge I think would you like a piece of
pizza yes that sounds nice how about
some cheese yes and a glass of orange
juice something's wrong with my computer
exactly what all I get is a blue screen
what's the matter I think I know because
this happened before what happened
before my hard drive crashed that's bad
news it sure is but I'm going to pull
Apple first just to make sure will you
lose all your files no I'm always back
up my files online you're smart
I called Apple about my computer what
did they say they said I need a new hard
drive that's too bad how much is a new
one about $400 it's so expensive plus
installation No my hard drive is easy to
remove and replace really yes it's just
a couple of screws that's nice it's a
lot better than paying someone $50 if my
hard drive
crashed I'll just call you okay